So, from one firstrounder to the next
first rounder.
>> It's nice to have two of them.
>> Very nice to have two of them. With the
24th pick last night, we took Texas A&M
wide receiver Casey Casspion in studio
with us. One thing that I think that's
been really cool since the pick last
night, Casey, is how your highlights are
starting to really make their way around
and you're a highlight factory, buddy.
You get the ball in your hands and it's
going to the paint. um when when you
think about this fit and how the last 12
or so hours have worked out for you,
where is your head right now in terms of
where it's at?
>> Man, you know, uh I'm just, you know,
excited really. Um you know, um you
know, uh a lot of nerves, you know, uh
but, you know, I'm just I'm just ready
to, you know, to get to work, honestly.
>> And that's got to be for you the fun of
this, right? Is to play football. That's
what you love to do. when you're coming
into a team where the new head coach is
an offensive guy and he knows his
receivers. He's had productive receivers
throughout his entire career and now he
wanted you here and now you're here.
What's kind of the conversations been
like with coach Monkin and he said to us
last night, I know you played some in
the slot, you played some outside, he's
like they see you as a number one
outside guy.
>> Yes, sir. I mean um the talks you know
um have just been you know um moving me
around um you know um outside you know
inside you know um
>> pump turn you know uh everything
everything honestly um I want to you
know um do you know uh as much as I can
um you know it just it it just brings
more value you know um to the team
>> you watch as as I did last night and
certainly aware of your you at Texas A&M
you guys had a hell of a And so you're
well aware when you're going to when
you're going to play Texas A&M, you got
to deal with you.
>> Um, and a lot of people didn't have a
very good job of dealing [laughter] with
you. It didn't go well for them. Um, but
when I when I I was telling my boys this
last night when we were watching the
draft,
>> what you're getting with KC is a weapon.
>> Yep.
>> He's a weapon. Like slot, outside,
motion,
>> jets, punt return, all of that. is a
>> when when you put all of that together
that that's really what you're getting
with you is is you're getting that
ultimate weapon. Um when you think about
when you've had the most success and I
mean gosh as a true freshman NC State
you got 10 touchdowns like you came
right out of the gate ready to go. Um
what offenses and and Todd has made no
bones about this. He's very malleable in
his offense. He wants to get playmakers
in space. That's part of it. When what
are you most comfortable doing on the
football field?
>> Everything honestly. Um,
>> I run the routes, uh, jet sweeps,
handoffs, screens, um, whatever they
need me to do. Um, you know, um, I
wanted them to do it.
>> 2025 Paul Horning award winner is the
most versatile player in college
football, first team all SEC as a
returner and as a as a uh, wide
receiver, more importantly,
>> consensus all-American. So, all the
accolades are there. You penned a letter
that talks about your journey, your life
story, things, the adversities and
things that you've had to deal with in
your life. But what I loved about it is
you ended with the most important part.
I am the best receiver in this draft.
You will not regret calling my name. I'm
thrilled you're a Cleveland Brown. I
think everybody who's listening is
thrilled that you're a Cleveland Brown.
How excited are you to take that that
story that you put in that letter, which
was very, very powerful for a variety of
reasons, and then to turn that now into
a spotlight. It's one thing to be a star
in college, right? the spotlight you're
afforded now and the stage that you're
afforded and the ability to impact
people and impact this city and this
team and people all around the world is
huge now. What does that mean to you and
the fact that you are so comfortable and
passionate about sharing your story and
being a beacon of light for people who
have a variety of struggles in their
lives?
>> Yeah, you know, um it's very important.
Um like I said before, you know, uh I
just want to be, you know, um
I just I just want to be that, you know,
outlet. um that you know uh that you
know role model um that you know person
you know who um who uh who gives people
who might not have as much confidence
you know uh confidence um you know uh I
just I just I just I just wanted to I
just wanted to share my story
because you know um
um to like
you know uh inspire people you know uh
who may be going through you the same
things, you know, uh who may be going
through, you know, um adversities to,
you know, uh
>> Yeah.
>> to push through.
>> Yeah. I mean, listen, we go through a
football season, there's a ton of
adversity, right? You know, this in
college,
>> you may have a big play, you may miss a
play, right?
>> You're not going to be phased by those
things. So, I think that is that's part
of the mental toughness, right? And the
self-awareness, the self-confidence.
These are things that Todd Mon talked
about in addition to obviously the great
skills you have, but
>> a lot everybody's talented to get to
this level, right, at some point, but
it's the people who have the fortitude
to maximize those talents and the
wherewithal and it certainly seems like
you have that and that's it's exciting
and I think what you're doing is very
powerful and I have a lot of respect for
it.
>> Hey sir, man, thank you.
>> Yeah,
>> you know, you and and I think our head
coach likes you a lot.
>> Uh there's no doubt [laughter] our head
>> He likes you a lot. Um and and you may
have been his favorite player of the
whole draft. Who knows? Uh but but he
had a guy who had some of the similar
attributes as you and Zay Flowers and
and last year in Baltimore when he was
the offensive coordinator, 86 catches,
uh 1,200 yards, five touchdowns,
>> first Pro Bowl receiver in their history
of that franchise,
>> right? And what he did with Zay was I
think what he probably envisions doing
with you. Uh not putting that on you as
a rookie, although I'm not thinking
you're going to shy away from any of it,
but just
>> I can do it for show.
>> I I [laughter] don't think you can,
buddy. Uh but what was that like
connecting those dots in terms of oh
that's how we you I can do those things.
>> Yeah. Um just you know seeing you know
um what Z Flower did you know uh the the
uh different ways they were you know
able to you know um get on the ball um
the short game screens you know um
intermediate routes you know um deep
routes you know um I can you know I can
you know do those same things you know
um if not more honestly um you know I'm
just I'm just you know honestly ready
>> and you know excited to you know finally
um play play, you know, inside of his
offense. So,
>> and I know the knee is good. You'll be
ready for rookie mini camp. So, that's
fantastic. Have you got a chance to talk
with any of the quarterbacks here? You
got some guys Deshun Watson who for a
while was one of the best quarterbacks
in the NFL. He's working his way back
from injury as well. Shador Sanders,
Dylan Gabriel, guys who've been very
successful in college and obviously
getting their start here with the
Cleveland Browns. Have you got a chance
to talk with any of the quarterbacks
yet?
>> Yes, sir. Uh so uh actually while I was
here on my 30 visit uh I uh talked with
um with uh with um Shador a little bit.
Um you know uh you know we talked you
know um and then and then uh after after
the draft um we know uh I texted shar um
I told him you know um I'm ready to
work.
>> Yep. I love it. I absolutely love it.
Let's go.
>> It's awesome man. People
>> it is exciting.
>> I would tell you this. You you played in
one of the greatest great atmospheres in
all of college football your last year
at Texas
>> crazy atmosphere.
>> Crazy.
>> And I mean this as a compliment to our
fans that that's what it's like here.
Okay.
>> The first time you go to a game day on a
Sunday at 1:00, you will feel the buzz
of the of this city through your car.
You will feel it. Um this is what we do.
We live and breathe and eat football up
here. And a football Sunday is sacred.
And if you enjoyed playing at Kyle Field
in front of those fans, you are going to
love playing in front of these and
they're going to love you. Yes, sir.
>> Uh it's going to be pretty special,
buddy. Yes,
>> sir.
>> Welcome to the Browns.
>> Can't wait, man.
>> Let's go. Let's go.
>> Casey Conpion in studio. Man, it's going
to be fun.